# Hveonwoo Cho

Seoul Korea

■ chochb123@gmail.com | • https://github.com/hyeonwoocho7 | • https://www.linkedin.com/in/hyeonwoocho/ | • khttps://www.kaggle.com/heoynwoo

#### Personal Profile

I am currently developing and researching an early diagnosis service using medical images in VUNO Inc. My main job is to develop an algorithm for lesion detection automation using 3D Lung CT. In addition, I have a lot of experience in developing such as object detection, segmentation, and classification in various domains including natural images and other medical images in 2D and 3D domains. Also, I am interested in domain adaptation, semi-supervised learning, and few-shot learning for the research. I published several papers related to the research topics mentioned. Furthermore, I participate in competitions such as a Kaggle because I like to find ways to solve problems from a data perspective. I recently won a silver medal at the Kaggle competition hosted by Google.

#### **Education**

**Kyushu University** Fukuoka, Japan

MS in Advanced Information Technology

March 2020 - March 2022

- GPA: 4 0/4 0
- Courses: Data Science, Programming for Data Science, Knowledge Representation and Reasoning, Statistical Theory and Methods, Learning Skills through Case Studies, Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, Statistical Learning

**Kyushu University** Fukuoka, Japan

BS in Aerospace Engineering

March 2016 - March 2020

• GPA: 3.4/4.0

**Daegun High School** Daegu, Korea

High School March 2014 - March 2016

## Work Experience \_\_\_

VUNO Inc Seoul, Korea

Al Research Scientist March 2022 - Current

- Collaborated with a four-person team to develop a product that detects and analyzes risk factors at an early stage through 3D lung ct.
- Developed 3D nodule detection model that find where nodule is in lung and 3D nodule classification model that classify if nodule is or not
- · Significantly boosted the model performance of the product from a data perspective by analyzing learning data from various hospitals.
- Technical Skills: Python with PyTorch, NumPy, Matplotlib, Pandas, Scikit-learn, C++, Ubuntu Linux, Linux tools, Apt, Scripting, Git.
- **Soft Skills:** Teamwork, Time Management, Communication, Presentation skills.

## **University Research**

#### **Domain Adaptation for Cell Detection**

Fukuoka, Japan

March 2020 - March 2022

Kyushu University

• Analyzed a video data from growing cell in different culture environments

- · Developed a new domain adaptation method for cell detection by the key observation for semi-supervised learning.
- Proposed effective pseudo labeling method based uncertainty and curriculum learning
- Research Keyword: Domain adaptation, Pseudo labeling, Multi-task learning, Uncertainty, Curriculum learning

#### Semi-Supervised Cell Detection by Tracking

Fukuoka, Japan

Kyushu University

March 2020 - March 2021

- Developed a semi-supervised method for cell detection by using cell tracking.
- Proposed a pseudo labeling method based on tracking that uses the mechanism of growing cells.
- Research Keyword: Semi-Supervised learning, Pseudo labeling, Tracking

#### **Domain Adaptation for Person Tracking**

Fukuoka, Japan

Kyushu University

June 2021 - March 2022

- Analyzed and handled multi object tracking datasets in various domains
- Defined a domain shift on a person tracking and developed domain adaptation methods using a center point based tracking method.
- Research Keyword: Domain Adaptation, Object Tracking, Pseudo labeling

## Skills

JULY 13, 2023

**Programming** Python (Pandas, PyTorch, NumPy, Scikit-learn. etc.), C/C++

Miscellaneous Linux, Shell (Bash/Zsh), ŁTFX(Overleaf), Microsoft Office, Firebase, Git, Docker.

**Soft Skills** Time Management, Teamwork, Problem-solving, Documentation, Engaging Presentation.

#### **Achievements**

2015	Pass, Korea-Japan Joint Scholarship Program	Korea
2021	N1, Japanese-Language Proficiency Test	Japan
2021	850/999, TOEIC	Japan
2021	Level6, TOEIC Speaking	Japan
2022	Excellent student award, Kyushu University graduation	Japan
2023	Silver Medal, top5%, 51st/1165, Kaggle: Google-Isolated Sign Language Recognition	Korea

### **Publications**

#### JOURNAL ARTICLES

Effective pseudo-labeling based on heatmap for unsupervised domain adaptation in cell detection

Hyeonwoo Cho, Kazuya Nishimura, Kazuhide Watanabe, Ryoma Bise

Medical Image Analysis 79 (2022) p. 102436. Elsevier, 2022

#### CONFERENCE PROCEEDINGS

Cell detection in domain shift problem using pseudo-cell-position heatmap

Hyeonwoo Cho, Kazuya Nishimura, Kazuhide Watanabe, Ryoma Bise

Medical Image Computing and Computer Assisted Intervention–MICCAI 2021: 24th International Conference, Strasbourg, France, September 27–October 1, 2021, Proceedings, Part VIII 24, 2021

Semi-supervised cell detection in time-lapse images using temporal consistency

Kazuya Nishimura, Hyeonwoo Cho, Ryoma Bise

Medical Image Computing and Computer Assisted Intervention–MICCAI 2021: 24th International Conference, Strasbourg, France, September 27–October 1, 2021, Proceedings, Part VIII 24, 2021

Cell detection for various cell shapes

Cho Hyeonwoo, Kazuya Nishimura, Ryoma Bise

Record of 2020 Joint Conference of Electrical, Electronics and Information Engineers in Kyushu, 2020

## Languages \_\_\_\_\_

**English** Professional Working Proficiency **Japanese** Full Professional Proficiency